Have you ever been in love?
Have you ever just looked at someone and...
Felt really loved.
And understood.
And protected.
Just find yourself praying.
For every second that you spend with them.
To stretch so that you can spend more time.
Together!
What?
You don't think it's possible for...
A young girl and an older man to be...
In love without any materialistic benefits.
I know that look.
That condescending look.
You looking at me as if...
You are better than me.
So now you think you know me.
Simply because you
have heard a few stories.
I've had that look for most my life.
And I honestly don't have
to take it from you too.
You only just got here Kali.
Why are you in a hurry to leave?
Keep the refund. I don't want to talk.
Write about it then.
Alright.
Fine.
In the beginning it started as...
It was just normal girl stuff.
No strings attached.
I was young beautiful. wild. free.
The world was mine for the take and boy.
Did I take as much as I could?
You can't just keep
a girl waiting like that.
I am sorry my baby.
I am sorry.
I had some daddy
duties at home with Joan.
So because of that I'll have
to be waiting for you.
You chose Joan over me?
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry
- Or let me...
- It was so impromptu.
That I couldn't just
talk over it over the phone.
Let me even ask you.
Who's your priority?
Me or Joan?
- You of course.
- Are you sure?
Because honestly it doesn't feel that way.
If you were.
you would not just choose her over me.
How can you even think about that?
Okay.
What should I do now to...
Bring my babies smile back?
Just take me home.
Just take you home?
Do they like this?
Who is that for?
Because I'm sure it's not for me.
I bought it for Joan but...
It's okay. it's fine I'll take it.
This looks so nice.
Wear it for me.
I'm sure even a daddy's girl like her.
Has to realize that
at some point.
That she can't always get
everything that she wants.
So jewelries are...
Ladies... Best friends?
Of course!!
I mean your jewelry is not going to...
Keep you waiting or lie to you.
- Look at you. Can we go now?
- Yes.
My goodness!
Just...
Feel the texture now!
Check out! Look at a dress.
Babe I'm telling you now!
Now I know the difference between Origo.
And Original.
No need for long talk. Babe take.
- These are beauttful.
- See it. Babe touch it.
- I love them!
- Touch it.
Gifts again?
Although my name is gift.
I don't receive gifts like this.
Whoever this guy is.
He must really be very rich.
Come!
When are we meeting this
your new guy?
That's true.
So he can introduce me to his rich friends.
I mean why are you guys talking like this.
You don't even...
You people talk all the time as if...
You've not been around rich people.
That's my problem with you girls.
These people are hardly ever around.
You should know now.
What's the problem?
Besides why are you
people even talking anyhow?
Just look at me.
As I'm fine like this.
Don't I deserve to be spoiled?
Babe!
-This baby girl
-Common!
- Don't I deserve a baby girl lifestyle.
- You do girl.
I wish I meet these
rich men and not those...
Broke boys that would
want to kill you in bed.
And they wouldn't give you anything.
It's okay Aunty. Keep quiet.
Do you like this one?
- I like it.
- Okay please take it.
Thank you!
You sounded like
you really liked this one.
I do.
- Take it.
- Thanks girl!
Take!
I got you girls covered.
Hello Daddy!
Daddy we need to talk.
I need new clothes.
Common! Common!
- Sit.
- Noooo.
It's okay sit down. Common!
Sir. I don't want to risk my
friendship with my best friend over this.
What about you locking the door?
Have some decency zaddy
Dece what? Common! What's decent about?
A sugar daddy.
And a sugar girl.
Besides you are not starting anyone now.
See. the riskier. the sweeter.
Really!
Sorry Daddy.
I went to go to a bigger
Supermarket to get you people drink.
(Stuttering)
You see. you see.
It's better late than never.
I thought you had classes now?
I did.
They got canceled.
I just got in like some...
-Minutes ago.
-Okay!
So Daddy
You remember my best friend Kali?
Oh my God! Kali!
- How are you my daughter?
- I'm fine Thank you.
- Good! Good!
- Thank you.
-Good evening sir. -She can never
stop talking about you at home.
Daddy. please where is the bracelet
you bought for me?
Bracelet?!
You see your daddy has
so much in his head.
I.
-I think it should be in the car
or something - Sorry. excuse me.
- It's Okay. it's okay.
- Hello!
I think it should be in the car
or maybe somewhere.
Daddy's pet.
You know to be fair on the guys. I...
I couldn't relate with them. I couldn't...
Relate with the guys my own age.
I didn't understand
what it meant.
To be with somebody my own age.
Didn't make any sense to me that the...
Girls in school were
dating the boys in school.
We are all just trying to
figure life out. You know?
And then even the ones that understood
life already they...
That had the answers.
They were all just out to use you.
Why your best friend's dad?
You know I just...
I just felt.
Instead of wasting my time. Why not.
Give myself to you know the
men who understood...
The essence of time.
the value of what they had.
Would you say you used your best friend
to get to her father?
They call Abuja the Haven of sugar Daddies.
Every corner.
Every street.
Has at least.
One Aristo.
Looking for young girls to spoil silly.
You were young.
Beautiful as you still are.
But you chose your best friends
Father.
Why?
You know there are two kinds of people.
There are the ones who lives their lives
to the fullest.
And end up being judged.
And there are the self righteous ones.
Who are too scared to live their lives.
Who are too scared to live
their lives.
And instead they make themselves
the judges over others.
I guess it's a way to make up for their...
Miserable excuse of a life.
At the end of the day.
People are a mass emotions and opinions.
Sometimes positive.
Sometimes negative.
It's just the way of the world.
Honesty however is personal.
Tea or Coffee?
Tea.
The end of my service year ushered
in many new things.
I finally started a
successful fashion brand.
My years of selling wears to students
and obsessing about.
Luxury designer wears finally paid off.
Cheers girls!
So guys I've been meaning to ask you.
What do you think about Umar?
I think he's the luckiest boy in Abuja.
Why would you say that?
But that is clear now.
Like the difference between
cigarette and cannabis.
You say the guy no be your spec.
And what do you think my spec is?
I laugh in french.
Old!
Must have grey hair.
With pot belly
Either married or not
that one doesn't matter.
But.
Chief Gozie.
Ambassador Felix.
Julius!
Okay it's okay.
Messaged received.
Just to mention a few.
Shocking though!
But wait.
How Umar take escape your
friend zoning moves?
Because plenty people have tried.
some even died on the way.
Okay wait.
I understand but it's not that deep.
Wait!
Do you remember George?
Our fine course rep you friend zoned.
That boy was fine.
That guy was ready.
To follow you to any length.
I didn't know you guys realized
what my spec was.
Kali.
Hold on.
Why Umar though?
After years of dating older men.
I got tired of the judgmental
looks and the side talks.
So I decided to finally try
someone my own age.
There is neither happiness nor unhappiness.
No.
Life at all he thought.
He was angry with all of them
for their interference.
Just because he felt in his soul.
That they.
All these people were right.
He felt that the love that
bound him to Anna.
Was not a momentary impulse.
Which would pass.
As worldly intrigues do pass.
He knew right then.
That they were going to spend the
rest of their lives together.
And make each other happy.
Why are you reading ahead?
No babe I did not.
Those are not Tolstoy's lines.
I'm writing our own story.
I love you.
You're the best.
Babe aren't you supposed
to say I love you too?
Common.
I don't want to lie to you.
Babe I want you to lie to me.
Even if it's for once.
I'll love to hear the sound of those
words from your lips.
I want to hear them.
I will.
I'll say it.
I promise.
When I mean it.
He was an absolute gentleman.
One of the good ones.
In Joan's words.
He was the salt of the earth.
- Let me. let me do this.
- Okay fine.
Alright just...
Make sure you spray tomato paste over it.
Add the cheese.
- Spray it evenly. make sure it's even.
- Yes boss. let me get the tomato.
You're so sexy when you are doing this.
Let's just put this guy here.
Watch and learn alright?
How am I learning from what I'm teaching?!
Yes.
Even even even!
I'm thinking I should
have spread it a bit more.
- Stop doing this!
- You are so...
I'm already a mess being
with you in the kitchen.
(Clears throat) Ladies and gentlemen!
For the 10th consecutive year.
The best chef award goes to...
Chef Kali!
Thank you! Thank you!
Please come and sit down.
Let's admit this is extra
ordinary. to be honest.
This is really good.
I mean you also helped so thank you.
I guess they should add
chef to my name as well.
I'm telling you actually yeah Chef Umar
that actually doesn't sound bad.
Welcome madam!
Umar how far now!
I wasn't expecting to see you here today.
I miss you too.
You do know I can not stay away from
this girl for too long.
You know now.
- How is work?
- Work is good.
Where are you coming from?
- Here.
- A meeting.
Thank you!
This is exactly what I needed today.
Oh God!
It's good.
Better enjoy it because this is
the last free slice you'll get.
- You cant be serious?
- I am.
And even you looking at her.
you too.
This is our house now.
I know that face.
What face?
It's the leave us alone so that we
can enjoy our company face.
And that's what happens when
you're loyal to a fault.
Like being in love with one
pattern of bedsheet alone.
You don't have to take the whole yogurt.
Common now!
- She left us two glasses.
- Don't mind her.
So was it about...
The money with the older men.
No. It wasn't just about the money.
Even though I didn't realize that it until
I started making my own money.
You know I've always liked the
idea of having my own money
So I could make my own choices.
When I was in school. I...
I became a personal shopper for...
Rich kids.
And I made a lot of money.
But you know even then people couldn't
believe that.
I was making my own money.
Because they felt it was the men
who were giving it to me.
It wasn't my fault that these men could.
Could spend money on people that
they love.
Without you even having to ask.
So what was it then?
I don't know.
I still can't explain it.
I mean they get me.
They get me on a deep level.
And the way they feel grateful for
having me in their lives.
That makes me feel good.
So did you find this deep
connection with Umar?
When I realized that I was only attracted
to older men I decided to break that.
I dated Umar as a...
Conscious decision.
To date people my own age.
- And how did that go?
- For awhile it was good.
I had the...
Care and support of my friends and Umar.
I had a business that was blossoming.
I wasn't happy.
Somehow I still felt lonely even
in a sea of people.
What did he do about this?
Nothing!
Umar was too...
Care free too.
Notice I wasn't happy.
And he was.
Too selfish to see that
I was no longer smiling.
Don't get me wrong Umar is a good guy.
I guess even good guys
have their own flaws.
When was the last time you
talked with your mum?
I don't know what's happening to me mama.
Lately I just.
Find my self so scared for my future.
I think I'm...
- Depressed mama.
- God forbid!
You are not depressed my daughter.
Depression is of the devil and you
have nothing in common with him.
Come.
Does this have anything to
do with your fathers death?
Babe.
When was the last time you saw your period?
Don't worry I am not pregnant.
That's not what I meant.
I'm talking about your mood.
it's been a bit...
Funny lately.
Yeah.
Wow!
So babe.
You do know that sex actually
helps relieve mood swings.
Yes.
It raises your endorphin's.
With other hormones
and it makes your mood...
A bit more lively.
Okay. so first!
I'm on my period.
But now I need sex?
Alright.
This is what I'm thinking.
I think we should go for a late
night movie. and when we come back.
We can have some.
You know. late night sex.
What do you think?
Goodness!
Babe!
Thinking back now I realize.
I was the problem.
It wasn't him.
It wasn't anyone else.
It was me.
Or maybe I'm too self-important.
I know that somewhere along
the way I've lost.
I've lost myself. I've lost my way.
But I don't remember where.
I have so many questions.
And no answer.
What answers do you seek?
Really thanks darling!
Don't worry about it. I
have the bills for today.
I just want to see that smile again.
- Look at me I'm smiling.
- I can see.
Joan. you said you'll speak to
your dad to help me out.
Or do you like how broke and jobless I am?
I can't keep spending
your money all the time.
I would also like to take my girls out too.
What do you think?
I'll tell him when next I see him.
-I promise
-Thank you!
You you are equally job hunting?
- You that wakes up at 12 pm.
- Is it not that serious?
You guys shouldn't bother yourself.
By the time I start making my millions.
I'll block both of you on social media.
Wait better still I'll
employ the both of you.
You!
You'll be my cook.
You are laughing. What can you do?
I don't think I can employ you.
I will just block you.
- So you'll rest.
- It's okay!
I can do.
- Do what?
- What do you want me to do?
- What can you even do?
- Anything.
- Tell me now.
- Please.
- I can work.
- You will ruin my company.
Something I will blow.
I've told you. come and hire me.
I am employable.
- I will make your business boom!
- You are funny!
Consider it.
Rest.
I will rest.
Hi!
You're good?
Your eyes are amazing!
You know that?
You shouldn't close them not even at night.
Would you mind taking a walk with me?
(chuckles)
Most men I've met would ask you
out for drinks or food.
I don't think I've ever met any man
who asked me out for a walk.
Well!
Most girls. will also be in there.
Drinking up and partying.
But here you are alone and clearly
you are not waiting for anyone.
So would you want to walk
with me while you?
Why do you think I'm not
waiting for someone?
Your eyes tell me everything.
And what else do they tell you?
That you have a lot to say.
So?
We walk.
You talk.
While I stare into those beautiful eyes.
After you.
I think there's a lot to
explore in this direction.
So you know somehow every body.
Just expects me to come into
their lives and make their lives better.
You know.
This feels like they feel I'm this...
Thing this good luck charm.
That once they have me all
their problems are just going to go away.
But it's not true.
- It's not?
- I mean at the end of the day.
I'm just as confused as the girl next door.
So you know one other
thing that feels really weird.
What?
Imagine this. picture this.
There is someone.
Who you...
Think you fancy.
Only to realize after a while.
That you never did and at that point
you were just lonely.
That's weird right?
You can't trick the heart.
It what it wants at the time he wants it.
Okay but I know
something that is even worse.
So?
The person you're beating yourself over.
Because you know. You're trying to...
Take their feelings into consideration.
And then at the end of
the day you find out that.
They didn't like you either.
And you were both just lonely at that time.
And using each other to pass away time.
So now you're just nothing
but a distant memory.
- Love is depressing huh?
- Yeah it is.
It is.
Do you know what will be really cool?
Tell me.
- Time machines.
- Sorry?
Yes!
Imagine a situation where everyone
has a time machine.
You can all go into the future
and see who the one.
Is.
Think about it I mean it will save
every single person.
A whole world of heartbreaks and...
And break ups.
We all just...
You know.
Know who we are with and
every body is happy.
But wouldn't that be a boring life.
Well a boring life is
better than a sad life.
You know. I mean it's not like
you can't have fun.
You can but you just know the person
you are having fun with is.
Definitely not the one for you.
And they know the same too.
I think it'll kill the joy of life.
If.
If I know what's going to happen tomorrow.
To be honest I will revel in the fact.
That I have what tomorrow
has in store for me.
See.
We both left home with different plans.
Neither of us knowing what the day
would bring for us.
Here we are. yet.
You know.
Here we are.
I think the stars are just aligning.
To...
Bring our footsteps together.
At this very moment.
Who are you?
Gil Thorpe.
- That's an interesting name.
- Yes.
Don't tell me you never
watched modern family.
(Both Laughing)
Women are usually more mature
than men their own age.
And the look for
relationships with people...
Who match their level of maturity.
It's a psychological thing.
Could this be the reason why you
were instantly drawn to him?
No.
It was more than that.
There was something about him.
Something about being understood.
There's something about talking for
hours without being judged.
I know we must have spent about
two or three hours talking and...
In that time I never.
Saw him bring out his phone.
not even once.
- Mobile phone?
- Yes!
I even had to pay him
a compliment for that.
You know...
I know you are seeing.
Someone now.
And honestly I respect that.
But...
I like you very much already.
You are someone I'd like to spend a long...
long time with.
Will you give me your number?
So I have an idea.
What if?
Instead of that.
What if we just meet back here.
where we met.
At 4 pm.
Next Sunday.
That's six days from now.
- In six days from now.
- Yes.
Okay!
You said Okay so quickly.
what if I don't show up?
It's Okay.
I'll keep coming here.
I'll come here next
Sunday if you don't show up.
I'll come every Sunday after that.
Do you know what?
I have an idea.
- What if we are to make a video.
- Video?
Yes!
Right?
So that way.
Even if...
Even if I don't show.
even if you don't show.
At least we would always
have a memory of this.
- Okay?
- Game!
Game!
Say something Gil Thorpe.
Something.
For the first time in my life I was
nervous about meeting someone.
I just wanted to look
perfect for this stranger.
Whose name I didn't even know.
(Whistling)
What's all these!?
Are you giving your clothes out?
You'll have to kill me
before that happens.
So why is your
room so scattered?
I'm.
I'm...
I'm looking for something
to wear for a date.
I need it to be as hot as it can be.
Since when do you need
to look hot for Umar?
Wait!
Is he about to propose?
- Joan. Joan calm down.
- Please.
As your maid of honor.
we need to talk about colors of the day.
What you thinking bro?
What you...
No No.
No.
So is everything okay.
Cos I've been hearing plenty
stories from him.
Yes.
We good.
Everything is alright.
Can I ask you something?
Have I ever said no?
Would you still...
Call it cheating if...
You know there's someone who is
always on your mind.
Not your partner.
Is that still classified as cheating?
Is this someone else the reason why
you ghosted us the other day?
What ever you are doing just think of Umar.
Because what you
guys have is good.
It would be sad to see you mess it up.
Please make my own.
Help me arrange the room I will.
Two tops only!
Don't worry leave it. don't worry.
don't stress yourself.
Say something nice.
Something.
(Laughter)
I finally lost all hope
in the relationship.
And It was really clear to me
that we could never work.
Kali!
Kali this is really impressive.
So your phone is actually working.
How are you?
Kali!
Why haven't you been
responding to my calls.
I'm sorry.
Don't sit there and
tell me you are sorry.
You have a lot of explanation to give me.
But first we are going to start.
With exactly what you've been doing.
With yourself for the past few weeks.
So I've curated a list of branding
and packaging concept designs.
I'm sending it you now so you
can start working on them.
As soon as possible Okay?
Alright.
Babe.
If I remember clearly.
You told me that you're
going to make it up to me.
Sure.
So I'm thinking.
That this is just the perfect time.
- My dad said he will like to meet you.
- Sure.
Why not?
When does he want to see me.
My dad died sixteen years ago.
- You of all people should know this.
- I'm so sorry It totally skipped me.
Babe I'm sorry.
Babe come back to bed now.
Don't make a mountain out of a mole hill.
Alright?
I'm sorry.
Okay wait. It's good I
have your attention now.
So yes. maybe I can finally do this.
Umar!
Do you know what my mum does?
Do you remember?
On the days. when
she's not selling puff puff.
She's going from door to door preaching.
Umar you and I we're not the same.
- Kali!
- It's.
I'm not one of you rich Abuja kids.
Okay?
And now that you know this.
Do you still think we can be together?
- That's what I thought.
- Kali!
Babe!
Hi!
I didn't think you'll still be here after I
stood you up for the second time.
Wow!
I'm sorry it took me two weeks
to come for our date.
- It's alright.
- And I wish I looked nicer I just...
I didn't have the time
to put on something else.
You're still the most beautiful
woman in the world.
Come!
I want to show you something.
Let's go this way.
This way.
So...
- I've never been at an art gallery before.
- Well!
Now you have.
- Oh this is so beautiful.
- Right!
Right.
It's all so beautiful.
That's exactly how I feel about you.
You're the masterpiece here.
How many more Sundays.
Were you going to keep coming
here. waiting for me.
Well!
When a man gets to his final bus stop.
There's only one thing left to do.
Head home.
(Inaudible)
- That's also possible.
- You know.
Give me a bit let me attend to this.
- I'll be right back.
- Alright.
Oh no no sorry. we haven't ordered yet.
Your dad did at the bar.
Are you guys like officially dating?
Kinda.
You have the I am in love eyes.
But I don't know if I should be
happy or sad for you.
Okay. calm down.
I don't know about love. but...
What we have is kinda deep.
You're weird.
How can you spend so much
time with someone.
And you don't know if you love them. How
can you spend so much time with someone.
And you don't know if you love them.
I just don't use love in the same
way other girls do.
You know? I just don't use love
in the same way other girls do.
You know?
So what happens to your boyfriend now?
-Ex
-Ex?
You see by the time Umar realizes...
How to read my body language.
He's going to see that we've been
over for a long time.
So you don't think he deserves closure.
Closure!
My darling!
Umar has his priorities and I can assure
you that I am not one of them.
So?
When are we meeting this your new guy?
(Inaudible)
Toke darling!
Let me officially introduce my two
favorite ladies to each other.
Toke meet Kali my friend.
- Kali. Toke my daughter.
- Hi. Toke.
It's nice to finally put a face to the name
I've heard so much about you.
Then how come I've
heard nothing about you?
Stop that.
Didn't raise you to be a rude girl.
- Sorry daddy but...
- No. enough!
Toke I'm sure we'll get...
A lot of time to get to
know each other better.
Not in this life.
- I'm sorry.
- It's okay.
So. what was that about?
Can't you see she's just a gold digger
who is trying to eat your money?
How do you know this?
Because it's written all over her face.
I know girls like them when I see them.
Why are you making
judgments based on face value.
Toke!
She is not what you think she is.
Can you just at
least get to know her?
Okay Daddy!
Please!
So is that a Yes?
No it's...
I don't know just...
It just feels weird.
What's weird about
going to see your mother?
Well for starters I've
never done it before.
Lucky you!
At least you don't have to...
Worry about taking someone else
after me to her then.
Okay!
Nice lines.
Though cute but. that's
not even what it's about.
What is it then?
I don't know.
That's fair.
I'll let you make up your mind.
Be rest assured. I'll support
whatever decision you make.
Kali!
So you even knew that what I'm
going to see on this phone.
I wasn't going to be happy.
Kali!
What the hell is wrong with you?
- This is...
- Shut up!!
Kali!
If you were looking for money
why didn't you just tell me.
If that was what you needed.
Instead of you going
about selling yourself.
To men for money. petty cash.
Look you have no right
to go through my phone.
It's private.
Kali. have you no shame?
Are you. Are you bloody insane?
Did you think about your privacy.
When you were selling yourself
to old men for money?
I can't even stand you.
I can't even stand you right now.
You disgust me.
Your dead father will
be cursing you right now.
Right now.
What's this nonsense?
What kind of nonsense talk is this?
That's why I don't even
like dating small boys.
- What kind of policing is this?
- Your phone!
Give it to me.
Your bloody phone.
You don't even have the decency.
To look me in the eye and apologize.
You know what?
You can have your phone.
Thank you.
You know that man is old enough
to be your father. right?
I'm glad your father is dead.
Because he would kill himself out of shame.
If he was still alive.
Shame on you.
Did you feel guilty?
No.
Do you feel guilty now?
Why?
Why should I?
You know. thinking about my relationship.
With older men and I'm realizing something.
One thing that never gets talked about.
Is the genuine connection.
People who have away of just mistaken...
Dating your own age
mates for compatibility.
What about trust?
Honesty.
Emotional self sufficiency.
These are words that I can tell
you that a lot of guys.
My own age have no clue about.
Describe your childhood in one word.
I'll do you three.
Perfect.
Lovely.
Beautiful.
Nothing compares with.
Growing up in the loving
arms of my parents.
When you get to your last bus stop.
The only way left to go is home.
That's something kola says.
You are the lord that is your name.
Nice home ma.
I'm pretty sure you did
not come all the way.
Just praise my home.
Kaliwana!
Come and sit down here.
You came to know.
If I will accept your relationship
with my daughter.
The answer is capital NO.
No.
The bible frowns at it.
Likewise myself as born again christian.
I am sorry ma'am.
I love your daughter.
She gives me happiness the
type that I have not...
Known since I lost my wife.
I love her.
I reject it in Jesus name!
What kind of love is that?
You want to use my daughter.
For replacement of your dead wife.
My beautiful pretty daughter.
You are using her to grief.
-No ma. No mama
-Just hold on. hold it!
Who is your mother?
I'm not your mother.
If not for anything you are older than me.
You see this thing that
both of you have going on?
It's evil.
It is caused by...
- Evil spirit from...
- Mama!
Shut up!
Shut up your mouth. Mama
What do you know?
Kneel down. let me
pray this thing out of you.
This devil. I say kneel down let me
pray this rubbish out of you.
I know you miss your father.
But this is not the way to go about it.
What is your problem Kaliwana my daughter?
I hope it's not what I'm thinking.
Mama you know this is the
reason why we are no longer close.
You never take any
time out to understand...
Anything or anybody all
you do is judge everybody.
You know.
Since we met.
I've been wishing for more time.
I really really would like to spend
more time with you.
Well!
- Me too.
- Really!
And again I'm really
really sorry about my mum.
Oh no please. that's
water under the bridge.
Now.
How about you tell me about
your family. everything.
No.
I'm sorry I'll rather not.
It's okay.
But.
It's you and I now.
Going forward you know that.
Thank you for being so sweet.
I brought something along for you.
Okay.
- I hope you like it?
- I hope so.
I got one for myself too.
Keep it.
I'm really glad.
That you agreed to do this.
After that. after the last time.
It really means a lot.
That you agreed to
come do dinner.
With me and my daughter.
Anything for your happiness Papi.
Thank you!
But.
Why do you fancy me?
Cos you are old and ugly.
Got you!
Not just sweet.
And you're loving.
And handsome.
And also I just feel like.
You know you probably deserve the most
beautiful girl in the world.
Such vanity!
Let's go in.
I'll get your door.
After you.
Daddy!
- How are you dear?
- I'm fine daddy.
So Okay!
It's not enough what you did to my cousin?
Umar told me everything.
You had to switch to my father.
I knew this girl was a gold
digger from the start.
Now go back to the bush you came from.
She's my girlfriend.
Look Dad!
Where did you pick her from?
I told you this girl
was gold digging whore.
- But you wouldn't listen to me.
- Enough!
You will not speak to her that...
That way.
- Now apologize to her.
- No dad!
Kola!
She's right.
What she said is true.
Kali!
Hey hold on. hold on.
Wait. wait now!
Kali!
- Hold on Kali.
- Kola please.
Please now.
Let's let's talk about this.
Honestly I stopped seeing him
immediately we started.
I believe you.
I had no idea you were related.
Look I know. I know.
Sorry for embarrassing you
in front of your daughter.
No It's... That's fine.
That's fine.
Kali. I love you.
Do you still love me?
If I told you...
That I used to sleep with men for money.
I'll still love you.
Why?
That doesn't even make any sense.
Who are you lying to?
- How am I lying?
- Yourself or me who?
I am not lying.
- I love you.
- Can't even deal with this right now.
No. Kali.
Leave me just stop. just stop.
I need to figure this out.
- Don't do things like this.
- Please.
It's Okay.
Alone. please.
Sometimes home isn't a place it's a person.
To love someone you
have to love yourself first.
I guess I just didn't love myself enough
to love someone else.
Kali. What again?
What again what?
Umar's uncle really?
I had no idea that was his uncle I swear.
I didn't know.
Right!
Just like you didn't know when...
Don't worry.
You could have had any man you wanted.
But you chose your best friends father.
Again.
Why?
This is not about Joan or her father.
That was in the past.
- Let's talk about your father.
- Okay.
We are even 30 minutes
past our session time.
Why did you come here?
I'll tell you why you came here.
A good percentage.
Of women.
Who loose their fathers early.
Or who had complicated relationships
with their fathers.
Subconsciously. look for father figures who
can love protect and adore them.
They may even seek a relationship
with an older man.
Who'll give them the affection that they
thought they missed in their childhood.
Could this be the reason
why women with Daddy issues...
Seek relationships with older men?
Stop!
You came to find answers
that you already have.
People with fearful -
avoidant. attachment issues.
Find it difficult to get
intimate with people.
They are afraid to
experience difficult feelings.
And emotions.
They exhibit.
Behaviors that are relatable
To.
Rebound dating.
And rushing into relationships.
Why do you seek?
When you know what you need.
Why do you lie to yourself and believe.
Please stop!
Okay. fine.
Fine!
You're right.
I was jealous.
I was jealous of what
Joan had with her father.
Sorry that I didn't care who got hurt.
I just.
I just feel like I've
been running for so long.
I feel like I've been
waiting for someone to
catch me all my life
and now I am so tired.
Are you okay?
I had a long hard look in the mirror today.
I didn't like what I saw.
I didn't like myself mama.
God forbid!
I reject it in Jesus name.
It is not your portion.
My daughter.
Come Come come.
- Come let me pray for you.
- Mama stop!
Please just stop.
Can you not see that what you
are doing is killing me?
Have you ever in even once.
Asked me how I'm coping with papa's death?
You've never despite the fact that you
know he was everything to me.
Then when I tried to talk to you about it.
You just say things that kill me further.
Can you not see that
your daughter is dying?
Your only child. How can you
not see that she's dying inside?
Mum I am not saying
that prayers don't work.
All I'm saying is.
Sometimes a girl needs her mother.
She needs her mother to tell
her that she loves her.
Tell me that Kali you are enough!
Please. My daughter Please.
Please. I'm sorry.
Look at me.
Please.
I may not know how to show
you for you to understand.
Or appreciate.
But deep down in my heart.
You are more than everything
in this world to me.
I love you!
Please forgive your mother.
You know I'm from a different generation.
The only way I know how to
solve problems is prayers.
It's only prayers my daughter.
please forgive me.
Please. I'm so sorry my love.
Please. please.
Please I'm sorry.
(Inaudible)
Joan.
I...
I have something
important I need to tell you.
O... kay!
I had an affair with your
dad when we were in school.
I'm sorry.
Girl why you...
Are you kidding me?
I've known all these years.
Wait!!
Why are telling me this now?
Cos I've realized how...
How wrong that was of me.
How much of a crappy
friend I've been to you.
I just felt you needed to know the truth.
The truth?
Did you even for one second think about me?
You've been calling me your best
friend all these years and yet.
You know at first I was upset.
But then I've realized my dad
has chosen his ways.
And you can't teach an old dog new tricks.
You were just one of his side chicks.
Or do you think you were the only one?
Well. the only person I felt for
was my mum. I mean.
When I found out that even she knew and
didn't say anything about it
Because my dad always
provided for the family.
And gave her whatever she wanted.
I just figured. why was I taking panadol
for another persons headache.
Joan I'm sorry.
Here!
For what it's worth I really needed
money at the time.
After awhile I got my best friend back.
I started a new phase of healing.
And acceptance.
Oh my God!
These are the new collections
I was telling you about.
I love it. I love all their designs.
Hands down my favorite
Nigerian fashion brand. So classy!
- You are getting one for me.
- Sure thing.
When I come back from my training in
Milan.
I'm going to order one of these.
- Oh my God. they are so beautiful.
- Are you telling me?
I'm buying all.
That's the gold digger
I was telling you about.
If not for my intervention she would have
been my step mum by now.
- Kali?
- Yes. you know her?
Yes. how will you know
fashion and not know her?
She's one of the best
in the industry.
- What do you mean?
- She's the CEO of Africana.
Wait. be serious now!
See?
And all this while I've been thinking...
- Toke come and introduce me to her now.
- Noooo!
Please now. I always wanted to meet her.
And take a picture with her please.
Okay. this is going to be super awkward.
- Hi.
- Hey.
Hi Toke.
Hi. I'm sorry about everything.
It's okay.
I'm sure you had good reasons
to say what you said.
- Still. I'm sorry.
- Stop. don't be so hard on yourself.
You know what?
I think I may have something just for you.
Play now!
Is that?
It's hold on.
Right.
God I shouldn't be
telling you the answers.
Are you serious?
Don't worry God will
reward me for my kindness.
Just call him already.
Well. for once I actually do not
want my happiness.
- To depend on somebody else.
- For how long?
You've already beaten your record for time
spent without being boo'ed up.
Truth is that. I've lost his number.
- I don't have it anymore.
- Okay!
I'm serious. pick two.
See vex.
Pick another two cos your mouth is sharp.
God!
Does anyone else think about the whole
concept of finding someone?
Connecting with them.
Falling in love with them.
Sometimes. I can't help but think
about the unlikely odds.
For many coincidences that have to happen.
For two strangers
to realize that without each other.
They are lost forever.
And when it ends. it's still beautiful
because you know that deep down.
You have been
touched by something deep.
Deeper than your trauma.
Deeper than your healing.
And both your lives will
never be the same again.
Hi.
I still wear it because I like you.
You know for the past
one month I've been...
Doing a lot of healing.
I've been facing my past
and answering questions.
That I've not ever dared to answer before.
And I realized that I've.
I hurt so many people in the past and...
The thought of finally loving someone and
then hurting them I just...
I couldn't do that to you.
I couldn't do that to my self.
I didn't even think I was capable.
Of giving you back the love
that you. that you give.
And that's why I ran.
I'm Sorry!
So where do we go now?
Kola always said that when love
is real. it would always find a way.
He had said a thousand beautiful
things to me that were right.
But this is the
one I'll always remember.